do you recommend going to specific
specialist ex urologist versus
endocrinologist versus others here's
what I'll say to that is if you know
this stuff and learn it you will be able
to tease through when you talk to
somebody you'll quickly figure out if
they know what they're talking about or
not when it comes to hormones that's
what I would say um that's the only
reason I knew anything about this stuff
is because I learned about hormones when
I was 17 18 years old for various
reasons obviously but I I I actually
loved the topic and so I just devoured a
bunch of this stuff and so when it came
time to go through med school and then
finally residency you know and stuff but
you hear what people start talking about
hormones and and you know immediately
that they're full of crap and so I
already kind of knew that and so that's
what I would say is watch the videos on
the YouTube channel go through the
introductory like the intro playlist
that you've made you know educate
yourself the best you can so that you
are the best expert you can be and not
everybody can devour this stuff but try
just do something to get the basics down
and then you're going to know real quick
and even if you go to an endocrinologist
or an ex eurologist or whatever that's
fine to try and then when they start
going okay we're g to put you on 100
milligrams every two weeks and an
aromatase inhibitor you go I'm not doing
that that's just what you say you don't
even go oh you don't bargain with them
you just go no we're not gonna be a
right fit unless you say I want to do
you know 60 milligrams twice a week to
start no Ai No this and they go okay
that's fine well then maybe you found
somebody that's at least reasonable but
in general you're not going to find
reasonable people when it comes to
hormone replacement in the traditional
medical community it's usually going to
be people that have probably already
left that system or never went that
traditional route to begin with not
everybody I mean you're going to find
Diamonds in the Rough but again that's
all just random and lucky you you
there's no great dat database to search
for help me find an insurance-based
provider that knows what they're talking
about and doing with hormones there's no
there's no good way to search for that
so you may just get lucky but in general
you're G to be better off probably going
with a cash pay type place but even then
it's it's a mindfield when it comes to
because a lot of the big box clinics
don't give a crap either and they're
just pushing product they don't and
they're pushing aromatase Inhibitors so
this is where again educate yourself so
that when you go and talk to these
places you know pretty quick whether
they actually have care about this topic
or not